Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: S Numbers, 1859-1864, 228559
  - Fugitt, James Preston, A Plea for Peace. Sermon Preached on Day of National Fasting, Humiliation, and Prayer., 17p., September 26, 1861; 228593 (Box 2, Folder S137)
  - Fuller, Richard, Mercy Remembered in Wrath, Sermon on Day of National Fasting, Humiliation, and Prayer, 24p., September 26, 1861; 228592 (Box 2, Folder S138)
  - Goodrich, William H., A sermon on the Christian Necessity of War, 15p., April 2, 1861; 228591 (Box 2, Folder S139)
  - Hibbard, John Randolph., A Spiritual Ground of Hope for the Salvation of our Country, 24p., August 6, 1863; 228590 (Box 2, Folder S140)
  - Mitchell, Arthur, A Word of Scripture to North and South, 32p., December 30, 1860; 228589 (Box 2, Folder S141)
  - Noble, Frederic A., Blood the Price of Redemption. A Thanksgiving Discourse, 21p., November 27, 1862; 228588 (Box 2, Folder S142)
  - Schenck, Noah Hunt., Christian Moderation: The Word in Season, o the Church and country. Whitsunday Sermon, 27p., May 19, 1861; 228587 (Box 2, Folder S143)
  - Schneck, Noah Hunt., The Memory of Washington, 32p., February 22, 1861; 228586 (Box 2, Folder S144)
  - Speer, William., The Lessons of 1860, 36p., February 3, 1861; 228585 (Box 2, Folder S145)
  - Thompson, M.L.P., Discourses Preached on the National Fast, Sept. 26, and Thanksgiving, Nov. 28, 22p., 1861; 228584 (Box 2, Folder S146)
  - Wadsworth, Charles., War A Discipline. Thanksgiving Sermon, 24p., November 24, 1864; 228583 (Box 2, Folder S147)
  - Curtin, Andrew Gregg., Proclamation [proposing a day of public worship in thanksgiving for the end of the war] on Thursday, the seventh day of December next, 1865; 228582 (Box 2, Folder S147b)
  - Curtin, Andrew Gregg., A Proclamation... to set apart Thursday, the twenty-sixth day of November, next, as a day of Thanksgiving and prayer, 1863; 228581 (Box 2, Folder S147c)
  - Potter, Alonzo, Bp., To the Clergy and Congregation of the Diocese of Pennsylvannia, 1861; 228580 (Box 2, Folder S147d)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church. Pastoral letter from the bishops of the Protestant Episcopal Church to the clergy and laity of the Church in the Confederate States of America 5p., November 22, 1862; 228579 (Box 2, Folder S148)
  - August, F.P., The Touchstone, 12p., 186-; 228578 (Box 2, Folder S149)
  - Breck, J. Lloyd., The second response to the Rev. Dr. Breck's appeal to the churches, 15p., 1863; 228577 (Box 2, Folder S150)
  - The Cleansing Blood, (Diocesan Missionary Society of the Protestant Episcopal Church of Virginia) 4p., 186-; 228576 (Box 2, Folder S152)
  - Daniel Murray, Late Lieutenant in the American Navy. Extract from a letter written by a pious lawyer 8p., n.p., n.d.; 228575 (Box 2, Folder S153)
  - Edwards, John Ellis. The Wounded Soldier. 8p., 186-; 228574 (Box 2, Folder S154)
  - A few prayerful words for the soldier 4p., 186-; 228573 (Box 2, Folder S155)
  - Hall, Newman. Come to Jesus 32p., 186-; 228572 (Box 2, Folder S156)
  - He Was Found Dead in His Bed, 186-; 228571 (Box 2, Folder S156a)
  - The precious Blood of Christ; or How a Soldier was Saved 4p., 186-; 228570 (Box 2, Folder S157)
  - Schaff, Philip.Slavery and the Bible, a Tract for the Times 32p., 1861; 228569 (Box 2, Folder S158)
  - Smith, Thompson L. The Good Soldier16p., 186-; 228568 (Box 2, Folder S159)
  - The Two Friends or, the Bible in the camp 12p., 186-; 228567 (Box 2, Folder S160)
  - Whipple, H.B. An appeal to reform the present Indian System 11p., 1863; 228566 (Box 2, Folder S161)
  - Douglas Monument Association. Organization, Constitution, and By-Laws of the Douglas Monument Association, together with an appeal to the public 19p., 1862; 228565 (Box 2, Folder S162)
  - Refugee Relief Commission of Ohio, First Semi-Annual Report of the Refugee Relief Commission of Ohio, 14p., November 1864; 228564 (Box 2, Folder S163)
  - Report by the Committee of the Contraband's Relief Commission of Cincinnati, Ohio 16p., 1863; 228563 (Box 2, Folder S164)
  - Southern Aid Society. Seventh Annual Report of the S.A.S. presented b the Executive Committee 48p., November 25, 1860; 228562 (Box 2, Folder S165)
  - King, Thomas Starr. Oration delivered before the Grand Lodge of Free and Accepted Masons of California, 1p., May 1863; 228561 (Box 2, Folder S166)
  - Sons of Oneida, Reception of the Oneida Volunteers at the City of New York, 10p., June 1861; 228560 (Box 2, Folder S167)
- Series II: Harwell Numbers; 1860-1865, 228535
  - Order of the Clerk. Photocopy, January 9, 1865; 228558 (Box 3, Folder H128)
  - Committee on Naval Affairs. Report on Promotions in the Navy (torn after flood), 1862; 228557 (Box 3, Folder H133)
  - Circular. Appeal to Farmers to Furnish Supplies to Army of Northern Virginia (2 copies-positive and negative), January 12, 1865; 228556 (Box 3, Folder H147)
  - Army of Northern Virginia. General Orders. Nos 21, May 27, 1861; 228555 (Box 3, Folder H148)
  - Army of the Peninsula. Head Quarters. Congratulations on Reenlistment 1p., March 4, 1862; 228554 (Box 3, Folder H169)
  - Nos. 6, 9, 12, 19, 28, 29, n.d.; 228553 (Box 3, Folder H222)
  - Morgan's Cavalry Division. Brigade Orders, August 22, 1862; 228552 (Box 3, Folder H232)
  - General Orders, August 4, 1862; 228551 (Box 3, Folder H233)
  - Confederate States of America, War Department. Circular 1p. (photocopy - damaged), June 26, 1864; 228550 (Box 3, Folder H366)
  - South Carolina Governor (F.W. Pickens) Circular letter calling for concerted action (copy 1 of 3 only), 1862; 228549 (Box 3, Folder H806)
  - General and Special Laws of the Called Session Tenth Legislature of the State of Texas, 1864; 228548 (Box 3, Folder H826)
  - Virginia. Adjutant General. Special Orders (copy), 1863; 228547 (Box 3, Folder H931)
  - Virginia Militia Orders. Companies A and B 160th Regiment (photocopy), June 28th, 1861; 228546 (Box 3, Folder H937)
  - Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth. Circular. p.1 only (photocopy), Nov. 27, 1862; 228545 (Box 3, Folder H939)
  - Davidson, R.O. The Artisans. Circular (photocopy), n.p. 186?; 228544 (Box 3, Folder H967)
  - Defense of our Capital! Request for enrollment in 2nd class militia (photocopy), 186?; 228543 (Box 3, Folder H68)
  - Longstreet, James. Notice to Soldiers of Army before Richmond. 1p. (photocopy), June 17, 1862; 228542 (Box 3, Folder H985)
  - Opelika, Alabama in Nomination for the Capitol (photocopy), 1861; 228541 (Box 3, Folder H1078)
  - Smith, James H. Regarding Relocation of the Capital of the C.S.A. (photocopy), May 23, 1861; 228540 (Box 3, Folder H1089)
  - Richmond Typographical Society. Constitution and By-Laws, with Amendments. 32p. (photocopy), Jan. 18, 1862; 228539 (Box 3, Folder H1147)
  - Smith, J.P. Reward for Missing Bay Mare (photocopy), October 16, 1862; 228538 (Box 3, Folder H1149)
  - Cooke, John Esten. The Song of the Rebel. "Jackson's Up"--Camp Talk. 3 cols. (photocopy), December 1, 1863; 228537 (Box 3, Folder H1225)
  - Boyce, James P. A Brief Catechism, 1864; 228536 (Box 3, Folder H1432)
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - Confederate States of America, Provisional Congress, Acts and Resolutions of the First Session, 1861; 228534 (Box 3, Folder C15)
  - Confederate States of America, Provisional Congress, Acts and Resolutions of the Second Session, 1861; 228533 (Box 3, Folder C16)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Acts and Resolutions. Third Session of the Provisional Congress, 1861; 228532 (Box 3, Folder C17)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Acts and Resolutions, 4th Session, Provisional Congress, 1862; 228531 (Box 3, Folder C18)
  - The Statutes at Large, 1864; 228530 (Box 3, Folder C19)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Statutes at Large. First Session. (defective: pp.49-56 omitted pp. [1]-16 repeated), 1862; 228529 (Box 3, Folder C20)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Statutes at Large. Second Session, 1862; 228528 (Box 3, Folder C21)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Statutes at Large. 3rd Session, 1863; 228527 (Box 3, Folder C22)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Statutes at Large. First Congress, 4th Session, 1863-1864; 228526 (Box 3, Folder C23)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Statutes at Large. Second Congress, 1st Session, 1864; 228525 (Box 3, Folder C24)
  - Compilation of the Tariff Act of the Confederate States of America, May 21, 1861; 228524 (Box 3, Folder C29)
  - A Digest of the Military and Naval Laws of the Confederate States, 1864; 228523 (Box 3, Folder C31)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Laws for the Army and Navy, 1861; 228522 (Box 3, Folder C33)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Tarriff, 1861; 228521 (Box 3, Folder C41)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Act Recognizing the Existence of War between U.S. and Confederacy, May 6, 1861; 228520 (Box 3, Folder C42)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Act to Further provide for the Public Defense, 1862; 228519 (Box 3, Folder C52)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. An Act to Organize Forces to Serve During the War, 1864; 228518 (Box 3, Folder C60)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. An Act to Amend the Tax Laws, 1864; 228517 (Box 3, Folder C66)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. An Act to Diminish the Number of Exemptions and Details, 1865; 228516 (Box 3, Folder C71)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. An Act Authorizing the Secretary of the Treasury to Borrow Specie to be Applied to the Redemption and Reduction of the Currency, 1865; 228515 (Box 3, Folder C72)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress Address, 1864; 228514 (Box 3, Folder C73)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress. Joint Select Committee to Investigate the Condition and Treatment of Prisoners of War, 1865; 228513 (Box 3, Folder C87)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress. Joint select committee to investigate the management of the Navy Dept., 1864; 228512 (Box 3, Folder C89)
  - Report of Evidence taken before a Joint Special Committee of both houses of the Confederate Congress to investigate the affairs of the Navy Dept., 1862-1863; 228511 (Box 3, Folder C90)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes. [Secret][Senate bill no.11] A bill entitled "An Act to provide for the further issue of treasury notes and for other purposes", 1863; 228510 (Box 3, Folder C102)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate, no.13] A Bill to be entitled "An Act in Relation to the Public Printing", 1863; 228509 (Box 3, Folder C110)
  - Wise, Henry Alexander. Letter from Gen. Wise. Headquarters 6th Military District, Department of South Carolina, Georgia, and Florida to Hon. Jas. Lyons, John R. Chambliss and other of the Virginia Delegation in Congress, January 3, 1864; 228508 (Box 3, Folder C130)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate Bill no.51] A Bill to provide supplies for the army and to prescribe the mode of making impressments, 1864; 228507 (Box 3, Folder C161)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate Bill no.109] An Act to amend an act entitled "An Act to Increase the efficiency of the Army by employing free Negroes and slaves in certain capacities", February 17, 1864; 228506 (Box 3, Folder C167)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes etc. [Senate Bill no.84] A bill to construe and declare more explicitly the meaning of "An act to increase the compensation of the heads of the several executive departments, and the assistant Secretary of War and the Treasury, and of the assistant Attorney General, and the Comptroller of the Treasury, and other officers therein named", June 14, 1864; 228505 (Box 3, Folder C168)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate Bill, no.92] A bill to exempt the cargoes of vessels owned by the States of the Confederacy from existing restrictions upon exports and imports, 1864; 228504 (Box 3, Folder C169)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate Bill no.119--secret] A bill to suspend the privilege of the writ of habeas corpus in certain cases, 1864; 228503 (Box 3, Folder C173)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate bill no.129] A Bill to provide for the employment of free negroes and slaves to work upon fortifications and perform other labor connected with the defense of the country, 1864; 228502 (Box 3, Folder C176)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Amendment to Senate Bill (129) to provide for the employment of free negroes and slaves to work upon fortifications, and to perform other labor connected with the defense of the country, 1864; 228501 (Box 3, Folder C180)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate Engrossed Bill, No. 121] A bill declaring the mode of ascertaining the value of the title deliverable to the government under the true construction of existing laws, 1865?; 228500 (Box 3, Folder C191)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Secret][Senate No. 157] A bill to provide for the appointment of a directing general of the armies of the Confederate States, 1865; 228499 (Box 3, Folder C196)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Amendment proposed by the Committee on Finance to the bill (H.R.229) to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption, 1865; 228498 (Box 3, Folder C203)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Resolution of the Legislature of the State of North Carolina in relation to the pay of disabled soldiers, 1865; 228497 (Box 3, Folder C204)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress, Senate. Resolutions Passed at a Meeting of the Fourteenth Regiment of Virginia Infantry, 1865; 228496 (Box 3, Folder C206)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [Senate, No.192] A Bill to Amend the Act entitled "An act to organize forces to serve during the war", February 17, 1864; 228495 (Box 3, Folder C219)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. Resolution passed by the General Assembly of the State of Virginia, in relation to the Confederate State impressment laws, 1865; 228494 (Box 3, Folder C222)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress Senate rules, 1864; 228493 (Box 3, Folder C230)
  - [Senate Report No.9] Report of the committee on finance on the bill (H.R.18) to lay taxes for the common defense and carry on the government of the Confederate States 14p., 1863; 228492 (Box 3, Folder C235)
  - Confederate States of America. Congress. Committee on Finance. [No.18--secret] Report of the Committee on Finance onn the bill(H.R.) to tax, fund, and limit the currency, 1864; 228491 (Box 3, Folder C236)
  - Senate. Report of the minority of the committee on finance on the bill (H.R.379) (photocopy), 1865; 228490 (Box 3, Folder C237)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House Bill] A bill to be entitled "An Act to Facilitate the Detection of frauds by the disbursing officers of the government, with the view to the discovery of frauds and peculations upon the government, facilitate the conviction of offenders, under existing or future laws", 1865; 228489 (Box 3, Folder C248)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. A Bill to be Entitled "An Act to Amend the Existing acts for the exemption of persons from military service", 1862; 228488 (Box 3, Folder C252)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House No.4] A Bill to regulate the navigation of the Confederate States and to establish direct trade with foreign nations, 1862; 228487 (Box 3, Folder C265)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House Bill No.4] A Bill to be entitled "An act making appropriations for the Executive, Legislative, and Judicial expenses of the government for the month of December, eighteen hundred and sixty-two", 1862; 228486 (Box 3, Folder C274)
  - C.S.A. House of Representatives House Bill No.5 to be entitled "An act making Confederate Notes legal tender...", 1862; 228485 (Box 3, Folder C277)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House] Amendment, 1863?; 228484 (Box 3, Folder C278)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House No. 21] Joint resolutions expressing opinion of Congress in relation to the conduct of certain citizens of Louisiana within the lines, and in the presence of the enemy, 1863; 228483 (Box 3, Folder C280)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House No. 24] Resolutions endorsing the recent proclamation and order of the President on the subject of retaliation, 1863; 228482 (Box 3, Folder C281)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House, no. 25] Joint Resolutions on the Pending War, and matters appertaining thereto, 1863; 228481 (Box 3, Folder C282)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill No.8] A bill to be entitled "An act to amend under military necessity and to provide for the indemnity thereof", March 17, 1862; 228480 (Box 3, Folder C283)
  - C.S.A. House of Representatives. House bill no.4 to be entitled "An act to prohibit quartermasters and others from speculating", 1863; 228479 (Box 3, Folder C284)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill, no.2] A bill to be entitled "An act to declare what persons shall be exempt from military service", 1863; 228478 (Box 3, Folder C285)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. Resolutions respecting the present war, and the causes leading thereto, 1863; 228477 (Box 3, Folder C286)
  - House. Amendments to a bill to be entitled: An act to declare what persons shall be exempt... (photocopy), 1863; 228476 (Box 3, Folder C287)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, Statutes, etc. [House Bill, no.12] A bill to be entitled "An act to increase and strengthen the army of the Confederate States", 1863; 228475 (Box 3, Folder C288)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill, No.8] A bill continuing to pay all discharged soldiers by reason of wounds and injuries received in the service, 1863; 228474 (Box 3, Folder C289)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill No.21] A bill to be entitled "An act to provide an expert duty on cotton and tobacco exported from the Confederate States to the ports or in the ships of any foreign country which has not recognized the independence of the Confederate States, 1863; 228473 (Box 3, Folder C296)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill No.8] Preamble and resolutions on the subject of taxes, 1863; 228472 (Box 3, Folder C298)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. A Bill to exempt certain persons from military duty, and to repeal the acts heretofore passed by Congress on the same subject, 1863; 228471 (Box 3, Folder C302)
  - Confederate States of America. Laws, statutes, etc. Mr. Foster's amendment to bill to fund the currency, 1863; 228470 (Box 3, Folder C304)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House No. ] A bill to be entitled "An act in relation to substitutes in the Army", 1863; 228469 (Box 3, Folder C305)
  - C.S.A. House of Representatives Mr. Garnett's Amendment, Feb. 20, 1863; 228468 (Box 3, Folder C308)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House bill no. ] A bill regulating the granting furloughs and discharges in hospitals, 1863; 228467 (Box 3, Folder C309)
  - [House Bill No. 3] A bill to be entitled "An act to lay taxes for the common defense, and carry on the government of the Confederate States" (photocopy) 24p., Feb. 25, 1863; 228466 (Box 3, Folder C313)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House bill no. ] A bill to be entitled "An act to provide certain regulations for holding elections for representatives in the Congress of the Confederate States.", 1863; 228465 (Box 3, Folder C314)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. A bill to be entitled "An act to provide for holding elections for representatives in the Congress of the C.S.A., in states occupied by the forces of the enemy.", 1863; 228464 (Box 3, Folder C315)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. Amendment proposed by Mr. Kenner, from Committee on Ways and Means, to bill "to lay taxes for the common defense, and carry on the government of the C.S.A.", 1863; 228463 (Box 3, Folder C316)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. A bill to establish a nitre and mining bureau, 1863; 228462 (Box 3, Folder C318)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. Communication of Tochman, touching his memorial now before Congress, 1863; 228461 (Box 3, Folder C319)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House No. 1] Joint resolutions on the subject of the war, and in regard to the free navigation of the Mississippi River, 1863; 228460 (Box 3, Folder C320)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House Bill no.27] An act to provide for the payment of officers acting under temporary appointment from the Commander of any department, corps, division, or brigade, 1863; 228459 (Box 3, Folder C321)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House bill, no.1] An act to provide for keeping in repair the railroads of the Confederate States necessary for the transportation of troops and government supplies, 1863; 228458 (Box 3, Folder C322)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes etc. An act to provide for holding elections for representatives in the Congress of the C.S. in states occupied by the forces of the enemy, 1863; 228457 (Box 3, Folder C323)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House bill no.6] A bill to regulate furloughs and discharges to soldiers in hospitals, 1863; 228456 (Box 3, Folder C324)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. A bill to distribute bounty, granted as a reward to the officers and men serving on board of the Virginia, Patrick Henry, Jamestown, Raleigh, Beaufort and Teazer, for their gallantry and courage in the naval engagement with the enemy's vessels in Hampton Roads on the 8th and 9th of March 1862, 1863; 228455 (Box 3, Folder C325)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. An act to prevent trading with the enemy or with persons resident in the United States, 1863; 228454 (Box 3, Folder C329)
  - C.S.A. Laws, statutes, etc. [House of Representatives] a bill to raise a tax for the support of the government, 1863; 228453 (Box 3, Folder C334)
  - C.S.A. [House of representatives No.23] An act to permit the funding of certain Treasury notes not now fundable, 1863; 228452 (Box 3, Folder C336)
  - C.S.A. [House of Representatives No.9] Resolution of finance, 1863; 228451 (Box 3, Folder C339)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.31] An act to amend an act entitled "an act to provide for the funding and further issue of treasury notes" approved March 23, 1863, 228450 (Box 3, Folder C340)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.15] An act to raise a revenue by direct taxation, 1863; 228449 (Box 3, Folder C342)
  - C.S.A. [house bill no.11] An act to amend an act entitled "An act to prevent fraud in the quartermasters and commissary's departments and the obtaining under false pretense transportation for private property" approved May 1, 1863, 228448 (Box 3, Folder C346)
  - C.S.A. a bill continuing in pay all discharged soldiers by reason of wounds and injuries received in service, 1863; 228447 (Box 3, Folder C347)
  - C.S.A. An act to amend the law in relation to substitutes, 1863; 228446 (Box 3, Folder C348)
  - C.S.A. [House No.7] Resolution directory to the select committee on finance, 1863; 228445 (Box 3, Folder C349)
  - C.S.A. [House no.3] Suggestions for financial relief, 1863; 228444 (Box 3, Folder C350)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.3] A bill to prohibit dealing in the paper currency of the enemy, 1863; 228443 (Box 3, Folder C351)
  - C.S.A. [house no.4] A bill to prevent trading with the enemy, 1863; 228442 (Box 3, Folder C352)